[{"answer": "Well, that's a good question.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "When you saw the video of Osama bin Laden in his lair in that compound, did you think it was a more damaging image than the one of him dead would have been if it had been released?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "I agree.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "If I was a member of al Qaeda, I'd be pretty disappointed that this was my great leader, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think the SEAL team, the special operators, had much choice.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Given that it's obviously so valuable, and we're already seeing material coming out which is clearly valuable, would it have been better under that circumstance to have taken bin Laden alive and to have tried to get key information out of him now that we know he was clearly still the figurehead of al Qaeda both in a conventional figurehead sense, but also an operational sense?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Well, it was pretty clear the White House -- most of all of this information came out of the White House.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Would you like to see them stop now and say no more about this?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, I was one of the sponsors of the Freedom of Information Act, and I do believe in as transparency to the extent it's possible.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "And shouldn't you just release this stuff?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, no one was waterboarded at Guantanamo Bay.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "And would you in light of the successful discovery and killing of bin Laden, albeit belatedly, would you encourage them to do more of this enhanced interrogation given that it appears to have been successful?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Were you as surprised as I was to discover where bin Laden had been hiding all these years?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Well, those are questions that ought to be asked.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Now either they are lying about knowing where he was, or they're the most stupid intelligence military in the world, aren't they?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Well, I do know that they have turned over -- they have captured and turned over a number of terrorists to the United States.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "We don't know, do we?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Well, we've had very good success in capturing or killing a large number of senior al Qaeda over the years.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Isn't that objective now achieved certainly in relation to cutting the head of his organization?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "I received a phone call from a member of my staff who had been alerted by someone in the press.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "When you heard the news last Sunday night -- and I don't know how you heard the news, maybe you can tell me -- that he was dead, did you punch the air?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Well, I think there is no question, Piers, that in the long-term it makes America safer.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "When you saw what we discovered there, do you believe that his death has made America safer or not?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "It was a very intense, very emotional day.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "How was the day for you?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, he certainly helped himself, and rightly so.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "And by doing what he did, Obama removed a key weapon against him by the Republicans that he is weak in foreign policy, didn't he?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "I don't know when you are going to hear about me, because I haven't really decided or focused on it yet.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "And when are we going to hear what you're going to be doing, Rudy?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "No, no I'm not.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "You're not on Twitter, are you, Rudy?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "I first started investigating the group, or what I knew that became the group, during -- just after the first World Trade Center bombing in 1993.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "What gave you the signs that they were going to be capable of that kind of outrage?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's hugely significant that he is dead.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Is that your take on things?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "It's very hard to say who will be in charge now.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "And who is now going to be in charge?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, in many ways he is like Gloria Swanson, the actress, looking at old videos -- old film to see how he looked.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "What did you make of all this when you heard about it?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Well, the question is who in the Pakistani government.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Does anybody high level really believe in the White House that Pakistan didn't know anything about bin Laden being right on their doorstep?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "I think it has been damaged.", "docId": "110509pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Do you believe it's been damaged as a result of what happened with bin Laden's death or do you believe that actually it may now going forward strengthen the ties?", "qSentId": 449}]